真爱字幕组
我在太空出生
Clarke voice-over: I was born in space.
却从未感受过阳光拂面
I've never felt the sun on my face
呼吸真实的空气  或者水中嬉戏
Or breathed real air or floated in the water.
我们谁都没有
None of us have.
三代人了  方舟号一直维系着
For 3 generations, the ark has kept what's left
幸存者的性命
Of the human race alive,
但现在我们的家园正在衰亡
But now our home is dying,
我们是人类仅存的希望
And we are the last hope of mankind,
百名囚犯被派执行绝地任务
100 prisoners sent on a desperate mission
前往地球
To the ground.
我们均因违法才被派遣到这儿
Each of us is here because we broke the law.
而地球上  没有法律
On the ground, there is no law.
我们要做的就是存活下去
All we have to do is survive,
但我们要接受地球的考验
But we will be tested by the earth,
它所隐藏的秘密
By the secrets it hides,
还有我们彼此之间
And most of all by each other.
地球百子  前情提要
Previously on "The 100."
地球百子
第一季第二集
真 爱 字 幕 组
我们知道他们已经着陆  但通讯系统失效了
We know they've landed, but communicatons are down.
这腕带会将你们的生命体征回馈到方舟号
This wristband transmits your vital signs to the ark.
取下它  方舟号会以为你死了
Take them off, and ark will think we're dying.
这就对了  他们把你驱逐到这儿
That's the point. They've dumped you down here
如同实验室的待死白鼠
Like lab rats to die,
那你为何还要帮他们呢？
So why are you helping them?
长官被射伤了
Chancellor's been shot.
已经有射杀者的身份了  Bellamy Blake
We have I.D.Ed the shooter-- bellamy blake.
我做了些他们一下来就会杀了我的事儿
I did something they will kill me for when they come down.
看见那山峰了吗？
Do you see that peak over there?
韦瑟山
That's mount weather.
穿过中间饱经辐射的森林
There's a radiation-soaked forest between us
才能有下顿饭吃
And our next meal.
我们成功了！
We did it!
这儿还有别人
We are not alone.
Clarke！快
Clarke! Come on.
Monty
Monty.
快点！  我们得快走！
Come on! We got to go!
Monty  起来啊！
Monty, get up!
他们是谁？
Who are they?
他们是什么才对
What are they?
我们搞砸了
We are so screwed.
Jasper  他还活着
Jasper. He's alive.
Clarke  等等  等等！
Clarke, wait. Wait!
等下
Wait.
避下那些树
Stay out of the trees.
他刚还在那儿
He was right there.
不  他在哪儿？
No. Where is he?
他们带走了他
They took him.
和我谈谈  Jackson
Talk to me, jackson.
谣言正在蔓延
Rumors are spreading.
目击者称看到运载机发射
Witnesses saw a dropship launch.
被人发现我们送百人前去地球
It's only a matter of time till the people figure out
也只是时间问题了
That we sent the hundred to the ground.
让安理会操这个心吧
Let the council worry about the people.
我需要你重建
I need you focused on reestablishing
和孩子们的通讯系统
Communication with those kids.
又有多少黑屏了？
How many dark tiles?
23个  一天内
23. We've been losing them at
均速失联
A steady rate all day.
Abby  但这些有所不同
Abby, these are different.
生命体征长时持续上升
Vital signs spike for a longer duration
在失联前  这看起来就像一个疼痛反应
Before flat line; it looks like a pain response.
这是我们期许看到的辐射反应
This is what we'd expect to see with exposure to radiation.
我知道  Jackson
I know what it looks like, jackson,
但肯定还有另一种解释
But there's another explanation.
我们只是还没找到
We just haven't found it yet.
长官在甲板上
Chancellor on deck.
我的儿子
My son.
- 我们让他们下去送死  - 不
-We sent them down to die. -No.
我们是为了他们求生
We sent them down to live...
去看看地球是否适合居住
To go to earth to see if it
这样我们就有救了
was survivable so that all of us could live.
Abby  别说了
Abby, stop.
我知道这很难接受
I know this is hard,
但我们不能在错误的希望上花费时间
But we don't have time for false hope.
这太空站正在衰亡  地球不适合生存
This space station is dying, and earth is not survivable.
这就是腕带所展示的
That is what the wristbands are telling us.
我们还不知道它要表达什么
We don't know what they're telling us yet.
Thelonious
Thelonious,
听我说
Listen to me.
请相信我
Please trust me.
我们都知道  这些孩子完全没事
For all we know, those kids could be perfectly fine,
包括Wells
Including wells.
捉着他！
Get him!
我们走！
Way to go!
我抓到了！我抓到了！
I got it, I got it!
伙计们  离开这！
Dude, get back here!
- 走！ - 拿着！
-Move! -Take it!
瞧见了？哈哈！
See? Ha ha!
嘿  你从哪儿弄得衣服？
Hey, where'd you get the clothes?
那两个埋了的孩子  在着陆时死的
Buried the two kids who died during the landing.
聪明  你懂的  我得拿走它
Smart. You know, I'll take it from here.
这儿总得有个市场啥的
There's always a market for--
让我们好按需索求  就像回到家一样
We share based on need, just like back home.
你还是不懂  是吧  长官？
You still don't get it, do you, chancellor?
这儿就是家了
This is home now.
这儿没你老爸的条款规定
Your father's rules no longer apply.
哦  不不  Atom  Atom  拦住他
Oh, no, no, atom. Atom, hold up.
想要回去？来拿啊
You want it back? Take it.
去拿那靴子！
Get those boots!
这就是你想要的？混乱不堪？
Is this what you want? Chaos?
小打小闹怎么了？
What's wrong with a little chaos?
Bellamy
Bellamy.
好好想想  我们是想让方舟号认为
Check it out. We want the ark to think
我们被地球整死了  是吧？
That the ground is killing us, right?
那做点儿小贡献就更好了
Figure it'll look better if we suffer a little bit first.
放开她！
Let her go!
你可以阻止这发生的
You can stop this.
阻止这？
Stop this?
我才刚开始呢
I'm just getting started.
打架了！
Fight!
你还不明白你不能掌控吗？
Don't you see you can't control this?
你死定了
You're dead.
等等
Wait.
公平对决
Fair fight.
啊
Aah!
这刀为我父亲！
This is for my father!
扔掉
Drop it!
Wells
Wells!
放开他
Let him go!
哇噢 嘿
Whoa. Hey!
够了 Murphy
Enough, murphy.
Octavia 你还好吗
Octavia. Are you all right?
还好
Yeah.
食物呢
Where's the food?
没能到达韦瑟山
We didn't make it to mount weather.
发生什么事了
What the hell happened out there?
我们被攻击了
We were attacked.
攻击 被什么攻击
Attacked? By what?
不 应该说是人
Not what. Who.
原来  最后一个方舟上死的地球人
It turns out, when the last man from the ground died on the ark,
并不是最后的幸存者
He wasn't the last grounder.
没错
It's true.
我们对地球的一切认知都是错误的
Everything we thought we knew about the ground is wrong.
这里还有人类
There are people here,
幸存者
Survivors.
好消息是  这表明我们可以幸存
The good news is, that means we can survive.
辐射不会杀害我们
Radiation won't kill us.
没错  坏消息是那些幸存者会
Yeah, the bad news is the grounders will.
戴护目镜的那个孩子呢
Where's the kid with the goggles?
Jasper被袭击
Jasper was hit.
被带走了
They took him.
你的腕套呢
Where is your wristband?
问他
Ask him.
摘了多少
How many?
24个 算算吧
24 and counting.
你们这些白痴
You idiots.
方舟承受生命的能力在下降
Life support on the ark is failing.
这也是他们送我们来这儿的原因
That's why they brought us down here.
他们需要确认地球可生存
They need to know the ground is survivable again,
我们也需要他们帮助我们在这里生存
And we need their help against whoever is out there.
取掉腕套 你们不仅仅是在杀害他们
If you take off your wristbands, you're not just killing them.
也在杀害我们自己
You're killing us!
我们没你想的那么弱
We're stronger than you think.
别听她瞎掰
Don't listen to her.
她是贵族阶级的
She's one of the privileged.
如果他们来地球  她会受益
If they come down, she'll have it good.
你们有多少人认同
How many of you can say the same?
我们能照顾好自己
We can take care of ourselves.
腕套 让你成为囚犯
That wristband on your arm? It makes you a prisoner.
我们不再是囚犯了
We are not prisoners anymore!
他们说会宽恕罪行
They say they'll forgive your crimes.
我认为你们本不是罪犯
I say you're not criminals!
你们是战士 是幸存者
You're fighters, survivors!
那些地球人该担心我们
The grounders should worry about us!
-没错 -对
-Yeah! -Yeah!
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
去找Jasper
Now we go after jasper.
Abby 你干嘛在这
Why are you here, abby?
你完全可以让助理来处理
We both know that you could have sent an apprentice to do this.
Kane在密谋委员会议
Kane's planning a secret council meeting
投票捕杀
To vote on the culling.
我想知道你的立场
I need to know where you stand.
我不会参加  你知道的
I don't have a vote. You know that.
Thelonious 他们听从你
They listen to you, thelonious.
你却不
Well, you don't.
我们看法一致时 我会
I do when you agree with me.
Abby 二氧化碳辐射防护能力在减弱
Now, abby, the co2 scrubbers are already failing.
缺氧症状普遍
The symptoms of oxygen deprivation are everywhere,
孩子症状最明显  他们会最早死去
And worst of all in the children; they'll die first.
你不必告诉我这些
You don't have to tell me that.
显然有必要
Obviously I do.
除非减少人口数量
Unless we act to reduce the population,
不然4个月后方舟上的每个人都会死
Everyone on-board this space station will be dead in 4 months.
我们采取措施了 送100个孩子到地球
We have acted. We put a hundred kids on the ground.
我们需要给他们时间
We need to give them time--
地球上有76个孩子 Abby
There are 76 kids on the ground, abby.
其中24人
24 of them,
包括我儿子 都死了
Including my son, are already dead.
我不这么看
I don't think so.
但你没有证据
But you have no proof.
拜托 别说了
Please...Stop.
我理解你需要对Clarke抱有希望
I understand your need to have hope for clarke,
但我是方舟的长官
But I am the chancellor of the ark,
希望渺茫
And hope isn't enough.
不要拖到人民处于险境的时候
Not when the end of the human race is at stake.
你想见我
You wanted to see me?
希望就是一切
Hope is everything,
我所选举的长官
And the chancellor that I voted for,
是明白这点的
He knew that.
我说完了
I'm done here.
Kane 别盯着我
Stop studying me, kane.
谁射杀的我
Who shot me?
Bellamy Blake
Bellamy blake,
一个工厂的守卫
A janitor from factory station.
偷乘运输机跑了
He stowed away on the dropship.
我们在调查他的帮凶是谁
We're still investigating who helped him.
我死后谁最受益
Who benefits most from my death?
有话直说
If you have something to say, just say it.
你急于处决挽救我生命的女人
You rushed to execute the woman who saved my life,
如果我已死  你现在已经是长官了
And if I were dead, you would be chancellor now
Abby也不会反对你
And abby wouldn't be here to oppose you.
我是依法行事 尽职尽责
I followed the law. I did my job.
你是代理长官
You were the acting chancellor...
工作职责绝不仅仅是依法行事
And this job requires more than simply following the law.
要知道有时不该如此
It requires knowing when not to.
我没想过谋杀你
I had nothing to do with the attempt on your life,
但对这次事件的发生 我不惊讶
But I'm not surprised that it happened.
你太弱 处理不了现在的局面
You're too weak to do what now has to be done,
我也不是唯一清楚这点的人
And I'm not the only one who knows it.
你在这啊
There you are.
当我父亲说他们
When my father said they
他们什么都没留 他是认真的
didn't leave us anything, he really meant it.
只是一个刮痕而已
it's just a scratch.
你交际能力很强嘛
You're making friends fast.
包扎好 可能会感染
Keep it covered. It could get infected.
不错的包啊
Nice pack.
嗯 安全带和绝缘带
Yeah, seat belts and insulation.
我还带了一些降落伞
I also packed part of the parachute,
或许可以用它来载Jasper
figured we could use it to carry out jasper--
好 把它给其他人
Good. Give it to someone else.
-你不跟我们一起走 -我的脚踝没事
-You're not coming with us. -My ankle's fine.
跟你的脚踝没关系 Wells 是你
It's not your ankle, wells, it's you.
你要回去等待援军 我会帮你
You came back for reinforcements. I'm gonna help.
Clarke 他是对的 我们需要他
Clarke, he's right. We need him.
这么长时间没有一个人自愿的
So far no one else has volunteered.
对不起 Monty 你也不能走
I'm sorry, monty, but you're not going, either.
怎么可能 Jasper是我最好的朋友
Like hell I'm not. Jasper's my best friend.
你太重要了
You're too important.
你在农田试验站长大 被招募为工程师
You were raised on farm station and recruited by engineering.
所以呢
So?
所以 食物和联系都少不了你
So food and communication.
这里的一切 都将拯救我们全部
What's up here, it's gonna save us all.
你想方法跟方舟号取得联系 我去把Jasper带回来
You figure out how to talk to the ark and I'll bring jasper back.
嘿 你准备好了吗
Hey. You ready?
我不准备去任何地方 你们也不应该去
I'm not going anywhere, and neither should any of you.
那矛能准确瞄准300英尺内的东西
That spear was thrown with pinpoint accuracy from 300 feet.
-那我们就这么让Jasper死里  -不会的
-So what, we let jasper die? -That's not gonna happen.
还太空漫步者呢
Spacewalker?
开啥玩笑
What a joke.
你觉得你是个冒险者
You think you're such an adventurer.
我认为你真的只是个懦夫
You're really just a coward.
这不是冒险 Clarke
It's not an adventure, clarke,
这是自杀行径
It's a suicide mission.
建一堵墙
Build a wall.
用那些倒下的树就好 我看着她
Use the fallen trees. I'll watch out for her.
Jasper看着你呢
Jasper looked up to you.
- 这到底是啥玩意儿  - 我不知道
-What the hell was it? -I don't know.
其他人说它看起来像一条巨型的蛇
The others said it looked like a giant snake.
你差点就死了
You could have been killed.
如果不是Jasper跳进去
She would have been if jasper
把她拉出来 她真的会死
Didn't jump in to pull her out.
你们要走吗  我也去
You guys leaving? I'm coming, too.
不不 没门 别再去了
No, no. No way. Not again.
他说的对 你的腿会拖累我们大家的
He's right. Your leg's just gonna slow us down.
我来这儿是找你
I'm here for you.
Clarke 你在干嘛
Clarke, what are you doing?
我听说你有把枪
I hear you have a gun.
很好  跟着我
Good. Follow me.
为啥要跟着你
And why would I do that?
因为你想让他们跟着你
Because you want them to follow you,
现在 他们在想我们中只有一个厉害的
And right now, they're thinking only one of us is scared.
Murphy
Murphy.
跟我走 Atom
Come with me. Atom?
我妹妹不能离开这个营地 清楚了吗
My sister doesn't leave this camp. Is that clear?
我不需要保姆
I don't need a babysitter.
谁敢动她一根毫毛 我不会放过
Anybody touches her, they answer to me.
走
Let's go.
你呆在这
You're staying here.
我会让你觉得你生活在地狱中
I'm gonna make your life a living hell.
这些人可不仅仅是恶霸 Clarke
Those guys aren't just bullies, clarke.
他们是危险的罪犯
They're dangerous criminals.
我就指望着呢
I'm counting on it.
什么时候我们开始一起营救别人了
Since when are we in the rescuing business, huh?
方舟号认为王子已经死了
The ark thinks the prince is dead.
如果他们认为公主也死了 他们就永远不会下来了
Once they think the princess is, too, they'll never come down.
我要那块腕带
I'm getting that wristband,
有必要的话我会把她手砍下来
Even if I have to cut off her hand to do it.
我去 Raven
Damn it, raven.
加压中 稍等
Wait for pressurization.
对不起 兄弟们 该走了
sorry, boys. Places to go.
没有人发现“B”号船坞没有任何损坏吗
Did anyone notice there's no damage to "B" Dock?
"B"号船坞是禁地 你知道的
"B" Dock's restricted. You know that.
怎么 他们要把我漂浮起来观察吗
What, are they gonna float me for looking?
呃 呃 呃
Heh heh heh.
亲们 别这样
Guys, come on.
刚刚发射出去了一艘太空船
An exodus ship was launched.
你们一点也不好奇吗
You're not curious about that?
那不是发射 是被喷射的
It was not launched. It was ejected.
据工程师反应
According to engineering,
日常维修的意外让他们飞出去了
A routine maintenance accident forced them to eject.
一个维修意外没有造成任何毁坏吗
A maintenance accident that didn't cause any damage?
这是个谎言 你也知道的
That's a lie and you know it.
好吧 如果你不想回答这个
Fine. Well, if that doesn't stir your tank,
那这个怎么样
How about this?
为啥他们当初造一艘运输船
Why would they build a dropship in the first place?
先停下好吗  我们需要检查你的身体
Just slow down, all right? We need to check your vitals.
我会让你省事的
I'll save you the trouble.
我感觉挺好
I feel good.
探监日 告诉那个亲爱的孩子
Prison visiting day. Tell lover boy I'll pay him
他出来的时候 我欠他两天的口粮
The two days' rations I owe him when he gets out.
现在3天了 放好我的装备
It was 3 days. Hey, stash my gear.
我一会回来拿走
I'll come back for it later.
好的 Raven 停下
Ok, raven, stop.
监狱的人在进行检疫
Lockup's been quarantined.
出现了一种病毒
There's some kind of a virus.
至少禁止探监两个月 对不起
There's no visitation for at least two months. Sorry.
我看见了 你在作弊
Hey, I saw that. You cheated.
伙计们 那堵墙不会自己建起来
Hey, guys, the wall's not gonna build itself.
墙不能阻挡住外面的东西 我们需要武器
Walls won't stop what's out there. We need weapons.
所以 制造武器嘛 看着
So build weapons. Look...
你哥哥不是开玩笑的 他会伤害他们
Your brother wasn't kidding about that. He'll hurt them.
得了吧 我们就是在说说话
Come on. We were just talking.
小伙挺性感 当我哥哥的婊子不错啊
You're too hot to be my brother's bitch.
我不是任何人的婊子
I'm no one's bitch.
嗯 不错
Mmm. Good.
来证明下
Then prove it.
跟我来
Come with me.
-嘿 哦  -出去
-Hey. Oof! -Get out of here.
不是任何人的婊子
Nobody's bitch, huh?
也许有一天你会意识到你无法控制我
Maybe one of these days you'll realize you can't control me.
知道吗 那个跟你在一起的家伙
You know, that guy you were with?
你知道他因为谋杀而被选中吗？
Did you know he was in for murder?
你想知道一些有趣的事情吗？
You want to know something funny?
实际上我在保护他免受你的伤害
I'm actually protecting him from you.
喂 喂 喂 喂！
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
你在干嘛？！
What are you doing?!
把你自己想象成被控制了
Consider yourself controlled.
这就是你所有的能耐？ 他们把我锁在地下16年
Is this all you got? They locked me under the floor
只是因为出生了
For 16 years just for being born!
这什么都不是
This is nothing.
额  你声音轻点吧？
Ahem. You want to keep it down?
我在集中精力
I'm trying to concentrate.
请注意  食堂将会关闭
Attention. The mess hall will be closed
从2100小时到800小时
From 2100 hours to 0800 hours
为了维修
For maintenance.
请注意
Attention.
食堂将会关闭 从2100小时…
The mess hall will be closed from 2100 hours...
Abby…
Abby...
Kane正在为了投票游说
Kane's lobbying for votes.
我们也该这样做
We should, too.
我们的机会在情况介绍会上
We'll have our chance at the briefing.
不好意思！ Griffin医生
Excuse me! Dr. Griffin.
我有个关于隔离检疫期的问题
I have a question about the quarantine.
我的男友在监禁室里  刚才我去看他
My boyfriend's in lockup. I went to go see him.
我看到了一根开着的通风管道
Instead, I saw an open air duct.
如果现在有一种病毒
Now, if there really was a virus,
难道你不会移动来容纳空气流？
wouldn't you move to contain the airflow?
病毒不在空气中
The virus isn't airborne.
这就是为什么管道打开着
That's why the ducts are open.
你能不能告诉我他还好吗？
Can you tell me if he's ok?
抱歉  我不能
I can't. I'm sorry.
不  你不觉得抱歉
No, you're not.
一开始是掉落的飞船  现在是这个
First the dropship, now this.
议会隐藏了一些事情
The council's hiding something,
我会弄清楚的
And I'm gonna find out what it is.
胆大的孩子
Ballsy kid.
是啊
Yeah.
她让我想起了某人
Reminds me of someone.
喂  等等
Hey, hold up.
为什么你这么急
What's the rush?
你又没有经历长矛穿过心脏
You don't survive a spear through the heart.
把枪拿开  Bellamy
Put the gun away, bellamy.
你为什么不做点什么呢？
Well, why don't you do something about it, huh?
当他们移动Jasper的时候他尖叫了
Jasper screamed when they moved him.
如果长矛重创了他的心脏  他会立刻死亡
If the spear struck his heart, he'd have died instantly.
这不意味着我们有时间浪费
It doesn't mean we have time to waste.
一旦你把手腕带摘掉  我们就能走了
As soon as you take this wristband off, we can go.
方舟号唯一能够相信我死了的方法就是我真的死了
The only way the ark is gonna think I'm dead is if I'm dead.
懂了吗？
Got it?
勇敢的公主
Brave princess.
喂  你为什么不给自己取个绰号？
Hey, why don't you find your own nickname?
你把这叫做救援派对？
You call this a rescue party?
我们需要分开  覆盖更多地方
Got to split up, cover more ground.
Clarke  跟我来
Clarke, come with me.
晚一点总比永远不做好
Better late than never.
我喜欢这么想
I like to think so.
我们比初次见面的时候多了些共同之处，对吧？
Guess we got more in common than meets the eye, huh?
我们没有任何共同之处
We have nothing in common.
没有吗？
No?
我们都到这里来保护我们爱的人
Both came down here to protect someone we love.
你的秘密在我这儿很安全
Your secret's safe with me.
当然  对你来说这是最糟的
'course, for you it's worse.
身边围着芬兰人
With finn around,
Clarke根本没有看到你
Clarke doesn't even see you.
就像你根本不在这里一样
It's like you're not even here.
他可能不是我真正的弟弟 但他一直在我身边
He may not be my real brother---- but he's always been there.
我的每段回忆里都有Jasper
Every memory I have, there's jasper.
我应该到外面去
I should be out there.
你不会要哭了吧？
You're not gonna cry, are you?
闭嘴
Shut up.
你确定吗？ 你弟弟不支持
You sure about this? Your brother won't approve
你帮助我们联络方舟号
Of you helping us contact the ark.
他不是我的守护人
He's not my keeper.
我们就这么做吧  我们就这么做
Let's just do this. Let's do it.
啊！
aah!
哦！
Ow!
婊子养  抱歉
-Son of a-- -sorry.
坏了  哦
-Dead. -Oh.
该死
Damn it.
如果我们不能把它拿下来
If we can't even take it off,
怎么才能把它变成一个收音机？
How do you expect to turn it into a radio?
继续
Go on.
我没事  还有事要做
I'll be fine. Work to do.
喂 Monty？
Hey, monty?
Jasper会理解你为什么留在这里
Jasper would understand why you stayed.
从小在地下长大怎样才能不成为一个极度焦虑的人？
How is someone raised beneath the floor not a total basket case?
谁说我不是？
who says I'm not?
因为他爱你
It's because he loves you.
你弟弟？
Your brother?
你不是一个极度焦虑的人因为你被爱着
You're not a basket case because you were loved.
是的  我是个幸运儿
Yeah, I'm a luckrl.
我不是说我比你糟糕
I'm not noying I had it worse than you,
因为我并不糟糕 Octavia
octavia, because I didn't.
但你有愿意为你做任何事情的人
But you have someone who would do anything for you.
我很羡慕这一点
I envy that.
我在想韦瑟山的事
I've been thinking about mount weather.
为什么他们不攻击直到Jasper渡河？
How come they didn't attack until jasper crossed the river?
这不是我们很安静
It's not like we were being
他们不知道我们在那里
quiet and they didn't know we were there.
他们等着我们渡河
They waited for us to cross.
那条河是一个边界
The river's a boundary.
这意味着韦瑟山在限制之外
Which means mount weather is off limits.
我们怎么才能拿到那些供应？
how are we gonna get those supplies?
我们该怎么解决食物?
What are we gonna do for food?
哇噢
Wow.
至少我们不用担心水源
Well, at least we don't have to worry about water.
哦  是的
Oh, yeah.
拜托  我们没时间考虑这些
Come on, finn. We don't have time for this.
Clarke  我们已经远足了好几个小时
Clarke, we've been hiking for hours.
我们需要休息一下
We need to take a break.
我们找到Jasper之后我会休息的
I'll take a break when we find jasper.
快点
Come on.
不要  不要
No, no.
Finn! 不要！
Finn! Don't!
滚  Finn！
Damn it, finn!
- 哈哈哈！ - 噢
-Ha ha ha! - Oh...
噢  哇哦
Oh, wow. Ok.
- 那就一分钟  - 好吧
-Maybe just a minute. -Yeah.
我知道你为什么如此执着找jasper了
I think I know why you're so hell-bent on finding jasper,
为什么你常关心他人呢
Why you're always taking care of everybody else.
你这会儿很像我妈啊
now you sound like my mother.
不过  继续  这很好
No. Go on. This should be good.
不守规矩的心理学家
The delinquent psychiatrist.
你救不了你父亲的
You couldn't save your father.
Jasper
Jasper.
他来过这里
He was here.
我们应该可以找到其他人
We should get the others.
我们已经很接近了
We're close.
Abby 我们要停手
Abby, we have to stop.
半小时后委员会选举就要开始了
The council vote's in 30 minutes.
我们还有30分钟
Then we have 30 minutes.
-从程序上可以看的出什么吗  - 看起来不太妙
-Anything from engineering? -Nothing good.
如sinclair所说
According to sinclair,
即使我们发信号下去  腕带
even if we sent a signal down, the wristbands
也不可能接收得到  孩子们也听不到
Weren't designed to receive, so the kids wouldn't even hear it.
我们肯定忽略了点什么  肯定
There's got to be something we missed, something
只是我们想不到而已
That we haven't thought of.
太好了 什么在解体？
Great. What's falling apart now?
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
很明显通风道被堵塞了
Apparently you have a thing for air ducts.
我打电话给安全部的人
I'll call security.
他们不是死了
They're not dying.
你想说什么？
What are you talking about?
那就是被送到地球上的人吗？
All that's being sent from the ground?
数据由此传输
Transmitted by these.
他们把它取下来了
They're taking them off.
什么？他们为何如此鲁莽？
What? Why would they do something so reckless?
因为我们说了不让取
Because we told them not to.
你好  小仙子
Hello, beautiful.
你想去哪？
Hey, where are you going?
没事
It's ok.
除了时间  我们一无所有
We've got nothing but time.
嘿  怎能知道我们没走错？
Hey, how do we know this is the right way?
不知道  漫步者认为他是追踪器呢
We don't. Spacewalker thinks he's a tracker.
这叫寻迹追踪  公元四年地球生存技能 他很棒
It's called "Cutting sign." Fourth-year earth skills. He's good.
你要把它继承下来？
You want to keep it down
还是要我在你背上把它画下来？
or should I paint a target on your backs?
看到没？
See?
都不瞧你
You're invisible.
那是什么？
What the hell was that?
我们最好把枪拿出来
Now would be a good time to take out that gun.
Jasper
Jasper.
-噢 天啊  - Clarke 小心
-Oh, my god. -Clarke, be careful.
Jasper？
Jasper?
这丫是什么？
What the hell is this?
Clarke！拉她上来！
Clarke! Get her up!
拉她上来！拉她起来！抓住！拉她起来
Pull her up! Pull her up! Get her! Pull her up!
你没事吧？
You ok?
没事
Yeah.
我们要把他放下来
We need to get him down.
我爬上去把藤砍断
I'll climb up there and cut the vines.
好 我和你一块去
Yeah, yeah, I'm with you.
不 你和clarke待在这
No. Stay with clarke.
看好他
And watch him.
你 我们走
You. Let's go.
他的伤口已经敷了东西
There's a poultice on his wound.
药？为什么他们会救他
Medicine? Why would they save
就为把他当成捕猎的新鲜诱饵？
his life just to string him up as live bait?
也许他们是想
Maybe what they're trying
抓住新鲜活物准备晚餐
to catch likes its dinner to be breathing.
也许他们想要抓住我们
Maybe what they're trying to catch is us.
数据显示那些在地球上的囚徒
Data indicates that the violent criminals in the group
终止信号的可能是他人的八倍
Are 8 times more likely to have terminated signals.
这意味着那些孩子们
We believe that this means that the kids
是故意把腕带脱掉的
Are taking off the wristbands by choice.
你对此怎么解析？
So how do you explain wells?
Kane是对的
Thelonious: Kane is right.
我儿子…是绝对不会自愿腕带解下来的
My son would...Never take his wristband off voluntarily.
孩子们都这么做了
Both our children have done things
这是我们从来没有预想到的
That we could never have predicted.
还是那个问题
The point holds.
孩子们需要更多的时间
These children need more time.
我们没有时间了
We don't have time.
修复生命支柱
Engineering needs 6 months
这工程需要6个月
To fix life support,
但是  我们在4个月内就会没有氧气了
And we'll be out of oxygen in 4.
没有人想这样
Nobody wants to do this,
但是我们面对无处逃生的事实
but the inescapable fact is that for every day
如果延迟  每天就会多牺牲10个人
We delay, 10 more people will need to be sacrificed.
今天是209人  明天就是219人
So today it's 209, tomorrow it's 219.
后天就是229人
The day after that is 229.
哪里还有人需要时间啊
Wee ones who need more time.
我们现在投票
I move that we vote now.
- 我同意  - 很好
-I second that. -Very well.
在要求四位主管投票前还有一事
The matter before us requires a 4-vote majority to pass.
最好的投票方式是让方舟号上209位市民投票
A vote in favor is to vote to cull 209 citizens of the ark
支持扩大生命支持的人们
From the supply grid in order to extend life support
和这些需要6个月时间的人们
For those who remain by 6 months.
都同意吗
All those in favor?
同意
Aye.
- 同意  - 同意
-Aye. -Aye.
谁反对
Senior council member: All those opposed?
- 反对  - 反对  - 反对
-Nay. -Nay. -Nay.
3比3
3 votes to 3.
长官将是关键一票
The chancellor will break the tie.
我们不需要问
we didn't ask for this.
我们是中间转型的一代
Ours was to be a transitional generation...
要保障后三代的安全
Ensuring that 3 generations from now
人们可以回家
Mankind could go home.
但是一切都变了
But everything has changed,
我们将是看着
And we will either be the generation that sees
人类返回地球的一代
The human race return to earth...
或者看不到
Or upon whose watch...
终于结束了
It finally ends.
我儿子已经在那里了
My son is already down there.
我送他去的
I sent him.
我不知道真相
And the truth is I don't know
他是否还活着
If he is alive or dead.
但是我还满怀希望
But I still have hope.
长官会投哪一票
Senior council member: How does the chancellor vote?
我不投
I don't.
先生
Senior council member: Sir,
如果您弃权  票数将会持平
if you abstain, the vote ends in a tie
10天内将会自动开始
To be automatically taken up again in 10 days.
每天就多10个人死去
That's 10 more dead for every day.
我再问一次  长官投哪票
I ask again, how does the chancellor vote?
长官弃权
The chancellor abstains.
我们还有10天
You have 10 days.
快点  murphy
Hurry up, murphy.
小心
Be careful.
这到底是什么啊？
What the hell was that?
地球幸存者？
Grounders?
Bellamy  枪
Bellamy  gun!
现在  她看到你了
Now she sees you.
有人叫了维修工吗？
Did someone call for a mechanic?
你就是那个预订工作服务的？
You're the one who called in the work order?
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
我说过我不会和你说任何事的  明白吗
Look, I told you I'm not gonna say anything, ok?
我相信你  你不会有麻烦的
I believe you, and you're not in trouble.
跟我来
Follow me.
你的意思是  目前还没有麻烦
Not in trouble yet, you mean.
这个水平超出了像我这样的人
This level's off limits for people like me.
但不是所有
Not anymore.
你知道我们已经送了百人去地球上
You know that we sent the hundred down to the ground.
你不知道的是为什么这样做
What you don't know is why.
方舟号要毁灭了  Raven
The ark is dying, raven.
生命承受力已奄奄一息
Life support is on its last legs.
我只有10天去证明地球可以生存
I have 10 days to prove that earth is survivable
否则他们就会裁减人口
Or they're gonna start reducing population.
320个无辜的人将会死亡
320 innocent people will be killed.
我不懂
I don't get it.
你为什么要和我说这些
Why are you telling me this?
我查阅了你的档案
I looked up your file.
你是方舟上50年来
You're the youngest zero-g mechanic
最年轻的零重力技工
On the ark in 50 years.
是52年 但这又怎样  Hanic
You're the youngest 52, but...So what?Hanic
所以
So...
你有9天可以处理这个
You have 9 days to get this ready
然后我就可以挽救一些生命
so I can survive a drop.
天啊 好大一块垃圾
God, what a piece of junk.
他们一定曾经发现过这个东西 在2102年
Theyust ha found this thing when they...
他们打捞3号空间站的时候
Salvaged mir-3 in 2102.
你想要我把这个有130年历史的逃生舱
You want me to get a 130-year-old escape pod
修理好 能再次承受地狱般的冲击
Ready to stand up to the inferno of re-entry
在9天之内？
In 9 days?
你能不能做到
Can you do it or not?
我可以做到  但是我要和你一起去
Hell, yes, I can do it, but I'm going with you.
不只是你一个人爱着地球上的生活
You're not the only one with someone you love on the ground.
这是我的条件
Those are my terms.
答不答应随你
Take it or leave it.
好吧  你可以和我一起去
All right. You can come with me.
你找到技工了
You got yourself a mechanic.
他们回来了
They're back!
在那儿
Over there.
- 他  - 他还活着
-Is he-- -he's alive.
我需要开水和一些可以用来包扎的布
I need boiled water and strips of cloth for bandage.
- 噢 - 噢
-Oh! -Oh, ho ho!
-谁饿了 -耶
-Who's hungry?! -Yeah!
Bellamy
Bellamy! Whoo!
爱 我有伤口
♪ Love, I have wounds
只有你可以让它愈合
♪ Only you can mend
你可以让它愈合
♪ You can mend
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
我猜那是爱
♪ I guess that's love
翻译：幸福ing形式    依依yiyi
我不能伪装
♪ I can't pretend
翻译：老马  小初  Dwyer
我不能伪装
♪ I can't pretend
实习翻译：Jojo   Joy
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
校对：幸福  依依  老马
真爱字幕组招贤纳士QQ群：319832261
我的皮肤是粗糙的
♪ Feel, my skin is rough
但是可以清洗
♪ But it can be cleansed
可以清洗
♪ It can be cleansed
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
我的胳膊很结实
♪ And my arms are tough
但是可以弯曲
♪ But they can be bent
可以弯曲
♪ They can be bent
嘿 嘿 嘿
♪ Hey, hey, hey
我想战斗
♪ And I want to fight
但是又不能
♪ But I can't contend...
他已经稳定了  但是没有药的话
He's stable for now, but without medicine...
他们把手表带摘下来换取食物
They're taking off their wristbands for food?
不 我不会这么做
No way. I--I won't do it.
你不用这么做
You don't have to.
我不能伪装
♪ ...I can't pretend
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
等等 等等 等等
Whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait.
你觉得你在不同的规则里扮演着什么角色
What, you think you play by different rules?
我觉得这里没有规则
I thought there were no rules.
嘿
Hey.
哦 感觉你的身体在长大
♪ Oh, feel our bodies grow
Atom
Atom!
你的灵魂浑浊了
♪ And our souls, they blend
快点  我们第一班守夜
Come on. We're on first watch.
耶 爱 我希望你知道
♪ Yeah, love, I hope you know ♪
我的心有多依赖你
♪ How much my heart depends
伙伴们 你们不能把我留在这
Guys, you're not just gonna leave me here.
不 Atom
No, atom.
我不会不遵守规则的
I won't be disobeyed.
我不能伪装
♪ I can't pretend
♪ I can't pretend...
伙伴们
Guys!
我猜那是爱
♪ I guess that's love
Bellamy
Bellamy!
伙伴们 Bellamy
Guys! Bellamy!
我不能伪装
♪ I can't pretend
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
我猜那是爱
♪ I guess that's love
我不能伪装
♪ I can't pretend
真 爱 字 幕 组
哦 哦 哦
♪ Oh, oh, oh
真 爱 字 幕 组